<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jonas Berg Skånøy</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jonas Berg Skånøy</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I got in! Plus some updates</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/igipsu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/igipsu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I finally got a definite indication: I got into Cognitive Science program at the University of Bergen! I&amp;rsquo;m very excited for what this entails, and especially to see what Bergen is like. I have used the past week (I found out that I got in only 4-5 days ago) to do some research on how my following semesters are structured, as well as to register and pay the student fee for it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Currently in the US, plus some updates.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/iminus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/iminus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;right-aligned&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/fromdownunder.jpg&#34;&#xA;    alt=&#34;On top of a skyscraper called &amp;#39;The Edge&amp;#39;. It&amp;#39;s a hundred floors down.&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Long time no seen, it feels good to be back blogging!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m currently on summer vacation in the US, more specifically the westcoast of Florida. We&amp;rsquo;ve been driving all the way down from NYC, which took us about one week, mostly because of sightseeing and the fact that we took our time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My thoughts on this semester.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whatsnew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whatsnew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;right-aligned&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/edinburgh.jpg&#34;&#xA;    alt=&#34;This was me, touching the David Hume statues toe while visting my friend in Edinburgh April last year. Had a blast of a time with the whole group who went down.&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This semester is going to be my final one as a bachelor student in philosophy! Am very excited to get started, and whilst what comes after is uncertain, I am very grateful for the chance I&amp;rsquo;ve been given to study something, simply because I like the subject. I am grateful for having a stable and safe family dynamic, who I can rely on both emotionally, but also with regards to practical manners. They have been supportive in my decisions from day one, and have been a huge help for me in the process througwards my own future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problems Regarding Political Debates in this Day and Age.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/truth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;right-aligned&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/truth.jpeg&#34;&#xA;    alt=&#34;You Can’t Handle the Truth&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, I want to put out thoughts on the topic of truth. More specifically, I want to look at how the modern understanding of truth as a rhetorical tool, rather than something that is practical in our everyday life. My motivation for writing this is to get my thought out on paper, as well as to express my disagreements with Ben Shapiro and Jordan Peterson on this specific topic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book review: Twilight of the Idols.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/toti_review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/toti_review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;right-aligned&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/toti.jpg&#34;&#xA;    alt=&#34;Twilight of the Idols&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, I’ll review Nietzsche’s famous work &lt;em&gt;Götzen-Dämmerung&lt;/em&gt;, better known as “Twilight of the Idols”. I will try, to the best of my abilities, bringing something forth the chapters I found most fruitful and thought-provoking. So, without further ado, let’s begin!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;quick-disclosure&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Quick disclosure&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#quick-disclosure&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This work might be one Nietzsche’s least nuanced work, and a lot of the stands he makes in it is a result of his declining health. This is the third to last book before his breakdown in 1889, and preceded both &lt;em&gt;the Antichrist&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Ecce homo&lt;/em&gt;. With that in mind, we should not brush off the arguments he lays forth as the words of a madman. Rather, it gives us some interesting perspectives into Nietzsche’s evolving thought through his philosophical career, aswell as his psyche.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the blog.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/welcome-to-the-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/welcome-to-the-blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s about time for me to start blogging! I&amp;rsquo;ve been putting off the idea for quite some time now (Just wanted everything else on the site to be in order first), but I&amp;rsquo;m finally doing it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll for the most part make blog posts on things that interested me, be that philosophy, technology, or whatever. I will also be posting updates to the site when I see that as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
